# SHILPA S NAIR UI UX Designer, Artist

#### **Personal info**

Address

Yokohama shi, Isogo ku Isogo – 3-6-1-1621 Kanagawa, Japan 230-0016

Phone

+81 70 6421 0228

**Email** 

Shilpaas2012@gmail.com

Date of Birth

1995-02-28

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/shilpa -s-nair-bab6bb212/

Portfolio Link

https://www.behance.net/shilpasnair

Skills

Figma

Adobe XD

Procreate & Sketch

Adobe Photoshop

Maya Animation

Video Editing

#### **Interests**

- Visual Media
- Interaction Design
- Art and illustrations
- Story telling
- Technical Art

#### **Hobbies**

Digital Art Music, Traditional art, Doodling, Travelling etc. Shilpa S Nair is a creative, self-driven Designer with a strong sense of artistry and forward thinking that is consistently displayed across all creations. As a trained graphic UI UX designer and 3D animator, she uses digital media as a tool for UI Design, Animation, illustration with eagerness to gain knowledge and experience.

# **Experience**

#### **UX Designer and Art Associate**

Kinz Entertainments (Indie Game Development Studio). Freelance

- UI Designer, Art advisor for the studio
- Worked for 4 Games published on Google Play
- Advisor for game aesthetics, Artist –UI, 2D, 3D, Pixel Art.

#### **UI UX Designer**

Coconut Punch Studio (Indie Game Development Studio). Freelance – Present

UI UX Designer for studio's "King Tornado" Game [Present]

#### UX Advisor, Art Associate - SCERT KERALA Govt.

SCERT Kerala (Contract). August 2023 – November 2024

- Develop unique and captivating Art styles for school textbooks
- Character design and visual artist.
- Assist teachers and faculty for UX design pipeline

#### 3D Animator - Movie production

Trishul Media Entertainment (TMEFX) – October 2022 – December 2023

- Worked on "Adipurush" Movie as 3D Animator
- Worked on "Jigarthanda Doublex" Movie as 3D Animator
- Collaborating with movie production pipeline.
- Creating Animations for Main, Side and Crowd characters
- Polishing and cleaning existing Animations

#### 3D Animator – Animation Studio

Toonz Animation Studio. April 2022 – July 2022

- Worked on a 3D Animation series as Animator
- Collaborated with Studio's 3D content creation team.
- Worked for character face animations, body mechanics.
- Polishing Animation curves.

#### **Animation Film Making Trainee**

Toonz Animation Academy. Sep 2019 - March 2022

- Traditional 2D, Digital 2D, Photoshop, illustrator, SketchBook
- 3D Modelling, Texturing, 3D Animation, Lighting, Arnold Rendering
- Associated with World Water Wise Program 2022 by UNESCO
- Worked on a short film project.

#### Certification

# Animation Film Making Advanced (AFMA) UI UX Design – NSDC India

# **Education**

Bachelor of commerce, 2017
Fatima Mata National College, University of Kerala

### Other key-points

Fine Art Teacher, Mural painting, Face Painting artist, Caricature Artist, Digital painting, Adobe Photoshop, MS office, Blender 3D.